trawell.in 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Trawell.in

### Introduction:

Trawell.in (a product of Tripzy Vacations Private Limited) recognizes the importance of privacy of its users and also of maintaining confidentiality of information provided by its users.

This Privacy Policy provides the practices for handling and securing user's Personal Information by Tripzy Vacations Pvt Ltd and its subsidiaries including Trawell.in.

This Privacy Policy is applicable to persons who purchase / intend to purchase / inquire about any product(s) and / or service(s) made available by Trawell.in ('User') through any of Trawell.in’s customer interface channels including website, mobile site, mobile app & offline channels including call centers and offices (collectively referred herein as **"Sales Channels"** ). 

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, wherever the context so requires "you" or "your" shall mean User and the term "we", "us", "our" shall mean Trawell.in. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, Website means the website(s), mobile site(s) and mobile app(s). 

By using or accessing the Website or other Sales Channels, the User hereby agrees with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the contents herein. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy please do not use or access our Website or other Sales Channels. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any website(s), mobile sites and mobile apps of third parties, even if their websites/products are linked to our Website. User should take note that information and privacy practices of Trawell.in’s business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which Trawell.in provides hyperlink(s), may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, it is recommended that you review the privacy statements and policies of any such third parties with whom they interact. 

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of User Agreement with Trawell.in and all terms used, but not otherwise defined herein, shall have the respective meanings as ascribed to them in the User Agreement. 

### Information We Collect:

**"Personal Information"** of User shall include the information shared by the User and collected by us for the following purposes: 

**Registration on the Website:** Information which you provide while subscribing to or registering on the Website, including but not limited to information about your personal identity such as name , gender, marital status, religion, age etc., your contact details such as your email address, postal addresses, frequent flyer number, telephone (mobile or otherwise) and fax numbers. The information may also include information such as your banking details (including credit/debit card) and any other information relating to your income and/or lifestyle; billing information payment history etc. (as shared by you). 

**Other information:** We may also collect some other information including but not limited to, 

  * Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities, buying behavior.
  * Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.
  * Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc.
  * Data Received from any third party including social media channels, including but not limited to personal or non-personal information from your linked social media channels (which include but are not limited to name, email address, friend list, profile pictures or any other information that is permitted to be received as per your account settings) as a part of your account information. 
  * Information pertaining any other traveler(s) for who you make a booking through your registered Trawell.in account. In such case, you must confirm and represent that each of the other traveler(s) have agreed to have the information shared by you disclosed to us.

### How we use personal information: 

The Personal Information collected maybe used in the following manner: 

While making a booking

While making a booking, we may use Personal Information including, cardholder names, credit/debit card number (in encrypted form) with expiration date, banking details, wallet details etc. as shared and allowed to be stored by you. We may also use the information of travelers list as available/linked with your account. This information is presented to the User at the time of making a booking to enable you to complete your bookings expeditiously. 

We may also use your Personal Information for several reasons including but not limited to:

  * confirm your reservations with respective service providers;
  * keep you informed of the transaction status;
  * send booking confirmations;
  * send any updates or changes w.r.t your booking 
  * allow our customer service to contact you, if necessary
  * customize the content of our website, mobile site and mobile app; 
  * request for reviews of products or services or any other improvements; 
  * send verification message(s) or email(s). 

In addition, you may look forward to receiving periodic marketing emails, newsletters and exclusive promotions offering special deals. 

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on the Website. To the extent these services are provided, and used by you, we will use the Personal Information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such Personal Information to assist us in making the Website the better and easier to use for our Users.

### Cookies and Sesson Data:

Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your device's hard drive. 

Trawell.in’s use of cookies is similar to that of any other reputable online companies. No Personal Information about User is gathered or stored in the cookies placed by a website or mobile site and, as a result, none can be passed on to any third parties. Cookies allow us to serve you better and more efficiently. Trawell.in uses cookies to personalize your experience on the Website and the advertisements that maybe displayed.

Cookies also allow ease of access, by logging you in without having to type your login name each time (only your password is needed); we may also use such cookies to display any advertisement to you while you are on the Website or to send you a offers (or similar emails – provided you have not opted out of receiving such emails). Focusing on destinations which may be of your interest. None of this information is passed to any third party, and is used solely by us to provide you with a better user experience on the Website.

A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used only for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our Website. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third party advertising companies or advertisement providers or servers. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of potential interest to you. The information they collect does not include your Personal Information.

The third party advertising companies or advertisement providers may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of the advertisements. All such information is anonymous. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is an industry standard technology and is used by all major websites. They may use this anonymous information about your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. No Personal Information is collected during this process. The information so collected during this process, is anonymous, and does not link online actions to a User. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Of course, by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. Trawell.in supports your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites. However, blocking Trawell.in cookies may disable certain features on the Website, and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the Website. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from websites you trust.

Automatic Logging of Session Data:

Each time you access the Website your session data gets logged. Session data consists of the User’s IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the User while on the Website. We collect session data because it helps us analyze User’s choices, browsing pattern including the frequency of visits and duration for which a User is logged on. It also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. The aforesaid information cannot identify any User personally. However, it is possible to determine a User's Internet Service Provider (ISP), and the approximate geographic location of User's point of connectivity from the IP address.

### Who is your personal data shared with:

Your personal information is not shared with any outside entity for any business or personal communication

Trawell.in does not sell or rent individual customer names or other Personal Information of Users to third parties except sharing of such information with our business / alliance partners or vendors who are engaged by us for providing various referral services and for sharing promotional and other benefits to our customers from time to time basis their booking history with us.

Companies under the same corporate entity

In the interests of improving personalization and service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with our affiliates, associate companies, our subsidiary or holding company or a subsidiary of our holding company or an entity which controls, is controlled by or is under common control.

If the assets of Trawell.in are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition. In addition, as part of business expansion/development/restructuring or for any other reason whatsoever, if we decide to sell/transfer/assign our business, any part thereof, any of our subsidiaries or any business units, then as part of such restructuring exercise customer information including the Personal Information collected herein shall be transferred accordingly.

### Disclosure of Information:

In addition to the circumstances described above, [Trawell.in] may disclose User's Personal Information if required to do so:- 

  * by law, required by any enforcement authority for investigation, by court order or in reference to any legal process;
  * to conduct our business;
  * for regulatory/internal compliance and audit exercise(s)
  * to secure our systems; or
  * to enforce or protect our rights or properties of Trawell.in or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing Personal Information of User(s) is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.

To ensure that the security and integrity of our services are safeguarded, we may monitor your Personal Information. This monitoring may include (without limitation) the filtering of incoming and outgoing electronic data messages to identify, limit and/or prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content.

Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we shall not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage.

### How your personal data is protected?

All payments on the Website are secured. This means all Personal Information you provide is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.

Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without notice. Changes to the Privacy Policy shall be applicable to each User till such time the User expressly withdraws consent or permission to Trawell.in to access/use the data.

You may always submit concerns regarding this Privacy Policy via email to us at [ support@trawell.in](mailto:support@trawell.in) . Trawell.in shall endeavor to respond to all reasonable concerns and inquires.
